icalshare.com 2014-11-22

# Privacy Policy - iCalShare

iCalShare is committed to protecting your privacy.

## What do we collect?

When you sign up to use iCalShare, we ask for your email address and name (optional). If you make a comment, we also collect your internet protocol address, user agent, and http referrer.

## How do we use your information?

Your email address will only be used to communicate with you. This means we will email you when you activate your account on signup, ask for help to reset your password, and for a limited number of other reasons that relate to the normal operation of this website.

When making comments, we will send your comment, internet protocol address, user agent, and http referrer to [Askismet](http://akismet.com/), a spam blocking service owned and operated by [WordPress](http://wordpress.com/). In most cases, Askismet will only use your information to make sure your comments do not contain spam. (You may also wish to read the [Askismet privacy policy](http://automattic.com/privacy/).)

Once your comment is posted, we will continue to store your comment, internet protocol address, user agent, and http referrer so that we can monitor comment usage over time and prevent spam, personal attacks, etc.

## What about advertising?

iCalShare displays a limited amount of advertising through the [Google Adsense](http://www.google.com/adsense/) program. Google may use cookies to record your internet protocol address to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. For full details on Google's policies, read the [Google privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html).

## Will iCalShare sell your email address?

No, iCalShare does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. iCalShare may provide aggregate statistics about our users, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable, third-party vendors, but these statistics will never include any personally identifying information.

## What about changes to this policy?

iCalShare reserves the right to modify this policy at any time. All changes shall be effective immediately, which means your continued use of iCalShare constitutes your acceptance of any updates to this policy. While we will make a sincere effort to notify you of any major changes to this policy in advance, you should check this page periodically to make sure you are familiar with the current policy.

## Have questions about this policy?

You can email your questions and concerns to [support@icalshare.com.](mailto:support@icalshare.com)

Last updated on January 1, 2010.
